subjectQuestions.cs = [
    {
        question: "What does CSS stands for what in web development?",
        answer: "Cascading Style Sheets",

        choices: [
            "Cheap Solo Stock",
            "Cascading Style Sheets",
            "Crafty Style Sheets",
            "Cultural Stunning Style"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "What is the mascot animal of Scratch language?",
        answer: "An orange cat",

        choices: [
            "An orange dog",
            "A yellow cat",
            "An orange cat",
            "A pink dog"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "What is an easy programming language that recommended for beginners?",
        answer: "Python",

        choices: [
            "Python",
            "C++",
            "Java",
            "Malbolge"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "What does boolean represent in JS?",
        answer: "true or false",

        choices: [
            "yes or no",
            "true or false",
            "correct or incorrect",
            "on or off"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "True or false: You can modify const variables in JS",
        answer: "False",

        choices: [
            "True",
            "False",
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "Where does the symbol @ come from?",
        answer: "Latin",

        choices: [
            "Arabic",
            "Greek",
            "Latin",
            "Was created for the need of email"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "List three types of error that can occur in programming.",
        answer: "Syntax, Logic, and Runtime",

        choices: [
            "Syntax, Oddity, and Logic",
            "Runtime, Environmental, and Paradox",
            "Logic, Inconsistency, and Runtime",
            "Syntax, Logic, and Runtime"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "What does DOM in Javascript HTML stand for?",
        answer: "Document Object Model",

        choices: [
            "Document Object Model",
            "Document Of Modeling",
            "Document Organized Model",
            "Document Object Management"
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "Is JSON and JS the same thing? Explain correctly.",
        answer: "No, JSON is only a data format, while JS is a programming language",

        choices: [
            "Yes, JSON derrived from JS, so it must be the same for most part.",
            "No, JSON and JS are different programming language",
            "No, JSON is only a data format, while JS is a programming language",
            `Yes, because there's "JS" from JSON`
        ]
    },

    {
        question: "Do you personally like Computer Science?",
        answer: "ALL",

        choices: [
            "Not really",
            "Stop minus 10 points then yes",
            "If I don't know CS then I would be gone already",
            "If there's no Mr. Tri"
        ]
    },
]